eh Karime sent me eye eh Because of the
eh Me manda Karime ojo eh Por el tema
mustache issue of the physique the problem that
del bigote del físico el problema que
this man has with me says Karime The
tiene este hombre conmigo dice Karime El
mustache in November is a symbol of the
bigote en noviembre es un símbolo de
fight against prostate and
lucha contra el cáncer de próstata y
testicular cancer, male Mental Health and
testicular la Salud Mental masculina y
suicide prevention Hey, I didn't
la prevención del suicidio Oye pues no
know movember
lo sabía movember
movember Well, I didn't know, I didn't know
movember Pues no lo sabía no lo sabía
Well pay attention to this movement okay pay attention
Bueno atentos a esta movida vale atentos
to this clip because this clip has this
a este clip porque este clip tiene esto
is wonderful this clip
es maravilla este clip te describe
perfectly describes what these people are Okay
perfectamente lo que son esta gente Okay
this clip perfectly describes what
este cl te describe a la perfección lo
these people are I hope that is
que son esta gente Yo espero que eso sea
something done with Photoshop Because I don't
un algo hecho con Photoshop Porque yo sí
go out on the street like that, no way eh we don't
la calle no salgo ni de coña eh eso no
know if it's a head of hair or a
sabemos si es una cabeza pelo o es un
Hindu turban But hey, it's up to taste the
turbante hindú Pero oye para gusto los
colors that
colores que la
fashion let's see Uy I think alne has
moda a ver Uy creo que alne se le ha
escaped a giggle under her breath what a
escapado una risilla por lo bajo que
nest or what a nest to the donkey let's see if you
nido ni que nido al asne a ver si tú
fall please I'll put it back from the
caes porfa lo vuelvo a poner desde el
beginning okay I hope that is
principio vale Yo espero que eso sea un
something done with Photoshop Because I
algo hecho con Photoshop Porque yo así
don't go out on the street like that, no way eh we don't
la calle no salgo ni de coña eh eso no
know if it's a head of hair or it's  a
sabemos si es una cabeza pelo o es un
Hindu turban But hey, it's all a matter of taste,
turbante hindú Pero oye para gusto los
fashion, let's see. Oh, I think
moda a ver Uy creo que al se le ha
a little chuckle escaped him what a nest, what a
escapado una risilla por lo bajo qu nido
nest, not even
ni que nido eso no lo llevaba ni ni
Elvis Presley wore that in his prime and he's pretending to be
Elvis presly en sus mejores tiempos y va
handsome if you're not handsome, man, you
de guapo si no eres guapo tío es que no
're not handsome, you're not even really
eres guapo no llegas ni a ser realmente
attractive and even though I've already done
atractivo y eso que ahora ya te hecho
your little touch-ups that make you look kind of something
tus retoquitos que parece medio algo
but before, it's even worse to be a
pero es que antes peor todavía er un tío
normal, ordinary guy, neither ugly nor handsome, you're not even attractive there will
normal y corriente ni feo ni guapo no
be
llega ni a resultón hab que habrá
women who find you who are
mujeres que te encuentren que quean
smitten by your words it must be because of your
rendida tus piedas por sera por tu
verbosity because it shouldn't be for anything else It's that
verborrea porque por otra cosa no debe
these people are
de ser Es que es que lo de esta gente es
incredible eh, it turned out, right? Look, look at
increíble eh resultó está verdad mira
that body Look at that body and what a
mira qué cuerpo Mira qué cuerpo y qué
fit of laughter we're going with one like that
ataque de risa vamos la una así
covering her mouth the other is turned
tapándose la boca la otra está vuelta de
away covering herself with the microphone up to
cara tapándose con el micro hasta hasta
the slime She's laughing and you should
el esmil Se está riendo y será para
see it too without a shirt down to the
verlo también sin camiseta hasta el
slime that's laughing at you let's
esmil que se está riendo de ti es que
go Yes, tattoos, tattoos
vamos Sí los tatuajes los tatuajes
look good, the underwear outside the
quedan bien el calzoncillo por fuera del
pants, beautiful, a little wide
pantalón precioso un poquito ancho de
waist no I hope you have corrected it the
cintura no Espero que lo ha corregir el
time that I was training and that
tiempo que llaba entrenando y ese
little chest lemon chest I don't know what
pechito pechito limonero no sé qué te
happened to you there Javier Oliveira I could
pasó ahí Javier oliveira Yo sí podría
say this This is comparing
decir esto Esto se compara
myself I don't know in what activity what
conmigo no sé en qu actividad qué
complex he could have yes the tablet
complejo puede tener sí la tableta
drawn like the other one who stuck to the
dibujada como el otro que se pegó a la
fence and salamar with the crop eh this This
reja y salamar con el buche eh esto Esto
is what you call this you are
es lo que tú llamas esto tú te estás
comparing yourself to me This is
comparando conmigo Esto se está
comparing yourself to me seriously or do you think
comparando conmigo en serio o te piensas
that you have hair on your head your whole life
que toda la vida tenes pelo en la cabeza
the head to have more things part of hair
la cabeza tener más cosas parte de pelo
listen to those beeps that must when it has they
escucha esos pitidos que deben cuando
are not if you have gone to the doctor do not
tiene no son si ha ido al médico no
go anymore they are not tinnitus that beep that
vayan más no son acúfenos ese [__] que
that neuron hears that dances inside you
escucha esa neurona que te baila dentro
that when it gets bored Silva is served from
que cuando se aburre Silva es servido de
the neuron ats over there of
de la neurona ats para allá de la
loneliness Hello from Ren
soledad Hola de Ren
Never head knee Tell the neuron that
Never cabeza rodilla Dile a la neurona
you have there grab The only
que tienes por ahí agarrar Al único
hair that is loose up there to
pelillo que tiene suelto í arriba que se
hold on tight hold on tight
agarre fuerte que se agarre fuerte
because it will be bouncing all over the
porque va a estar rebotando por toda la
head of that hollow that it has that looks like
cabeza de esa hueca que tiene que parece
a knee when I tell you this little
una rodilla cuando te cuente este
secret
secretito
but  this little secret for you for me only
pero este secretito para ti para m nada
this little secret for you for me
má este secretito para ti para m nada
only the one from Troy the video that you're
más el de Troya el vídeo que estás
putting on screen right now the
poniendo ahora mismo en pantalla el
video that you just ate the one you
vídeo que te acabas de comer del que te
're laughing at is a
estás riendo tú es un
stupid edit it's an edit you just ate
edit tonto es un edit te acabas de comer
an edit of these harassment accounts
un edit de las cuentas estas de acoso
that manipulate clips To make me look bad or
que manipulan clips Para dejarme mal o
try to invent things that I've
intentar inventarse cosas que yo he
said and I'm not saying it's a stupid edit to
dicho y no digo es un edit tonto de
eat an edit okay
comer un edit vale
and this clip of course is that with these people
e este clip claro es que con esta gente
what is there
qué es lo que hay
eh This video that is watching the one from
eh Este vídeo que está viendo al de
Troy in which he says that Alanne is
Troya en el que dice que que alanne se
laughing that the other one is laughing that Lena
ríe que el otro se ríe que la Lena se
is covering her mouth is an edit we are
está tapando la boca es un edit estamos
there looking at Peppa's photos do you
ahí viendo las fotos de la Peppa os
remember the photo This is an edit the photo
acordáis la foto Esta es un edit la foto
This is an edit that it is true that I have
Esta es un edit que sí que es verdad que
the quiff combed high Okay
tengo ahí el tupé bien peinado alto Vale
but not that much I mean it's an edit
pero no tanto o sea es un edit
Okay look here is the one that you are
Okay mira aquí está la que tú estás
putting on screen the one from Troy the one that
poniendo en pantalla al de Troya la que
you are putting on screen and there
tú estás poniendo en pantalla y ahí
you have the photo on instagram original
tienes la foto en instagram original
man yes man aloria yes you yes you  you
hombre si hombre aloria si tú si tú te
see yourself Yes you do Yes you see yourself Yes you see yourself that
ves Si tú si tú te ves Si tú te ves que
you
tú
compete Yes you see yourself Yes you have that
compites si tú te ves si tú tienes esa
self-esteem and you say that you saw yourself
autoestima y tú dices que tú te veías
better at my age I'm very happy
mejor con mi edad me alegro muchísimo
man I'm very happy, I really am I mean I
tío me alegro muchísimo yo de verdad O
would sign to reach 95 years old
sea firmaría por llegar a los 95 años
being at least like you I would really sign I have to admit that I would
estando por lo menos como tú yo firmaba
sign to be like you When I turn
firmaba por estar como tú Cuando cumpla
95 if I get there okay I would sign but this
95 si llego vale que firmaba pero este
video that you're putting there like the
vídeo que estás poniendo tú ahí como la
great thing is an edit of course you're better
gran cosa es un edit claro estás mejor
now too I tell you Yeah well let's see of
ahora también te digo Sí bueno a ver
course It's that here this I understand that if I
claro Es que aquí esto entiendo que si
have these clothes this is January 14th of
tengo esta ropa esto es 14 de enero
course January 14th there more or less I got
claro 14 de enero ahí más o menos me
a little bit fatter again
volví a poner un poquito más gordito
okay and now in April May is when I
vale y ahora en abril Mayo es cuando
started with him with the coach Román a
empecé con el con el entrenador Román un
kiss
beso
handsome in May I started with the coach
guapo en mayo Empecé con el entrenador
okay this photo that I'm putting that I would
vale esta foto que estoy poniendo que yo
say this I would have to check it I
diría esto ya lo tendría que comprobar
don't have it on hand because these these
no la tengo a mano porque esto estas
photos I don't know if I have them I don't even
fotos no sé si las tengo ni siquiera
think that these photos are
creo que estas fotos son
from I think these photos are let's see if I
del Creo que estas fotos son a ver si
have them on hand  you are a loser but
las tengo a mano eres un pringado pero
always be careful dude it's
de mucho cuidado siempre tío es que
clear that with these people then they think
claro con son la gente luego se piensa
that these people are actors that I put
que esta gente son actores que yo pongo
here to laugh to create content
aquí para reírme para crear contenido
but no no no that they are like that they are stupid that they
pero no no que son así que son tontos
are stupid let's see I would say It's that I don't
que son tontos a ver yo diría Es que no
have the same the same photo I don't have it
tengo la misma la misma foto no la tengo
at hand I think eh Wait I know that those
yo a mano creo eh Espérate sé que esas
photos are of the physical change and that photo
fotos son del cambio físico y esa foto
is not clear it's that to me when I have
no es claro es que a mí cuando yo he
seen that video I say What am I doing in a
visto ese vídeo digo Qué hago yo en un
friky tuber putting those photos no e What am
friky tuber poniendo esas fotos no
I doing in a fraker putting those
e Qué hago yo en un fraker poniendo esas
photos no yes these photos not even No
fotos no si estas fotos ni siquiera No
here this photo photos are from
aquí esta foto fotos son del verano
last summer when I did a super
pasado que yo hice una dieta super
strict diet and I was taking photos because I
estricta y me iba haciendo fotos porque
managed to lose a lot of weight okay it
llegué a perder un montón de kilos vale
was the diet let's say that it made me dizzy and everything is
era la dieta vamos que me mareaba y todo
worth I would say that here this curve
vale Yo diría que aquí esta curva de
here is edited but no I'm not
aquí está editada pero no no lo tengo
sure eh Maybe they are photos in front
seguro eh A lo mejor son fotos delantes
during I was losing my belly that I
durante iba perdiendo la barriga que me
remember I could see the
acuerdo Yo que se me llegó a ver la
tablet what the [ __ ] [ __ ] you can see the
tableta que que [__] [__] se me ve la
tablet and I'm barely doing abdomen
tableta y apenas estoy haciendo abdomen
you understand but of course it's an edit dude it's
me entiendes pero claro es un edit tío
that  you start following these
es que os ponéis a seguir las cuent
harassment accounts where are these accounts They
estas de acoso dónde están estas cuentas
can only give him the balls stalkers
Solamente le pueden dar bolas acosadores
dude learning geography with Javi
tío aprendiendo geografía con Javi
oliveira Costa Brava What is it I mean I see
oliveira Costa Brava Qué es O sea me veo
Tania I heard Tania the other
a la Tania Me escuché a la Tania el otro
day on these clis that you sent me No
día en los cli estos que me mandaste No
where was she defending Loli
donde estaba defendiendo a la Loli
repeating to me over and over again I don't know what about the
repetirme una y otra vez no sé qué de la
Costa Brava I don't know what about the Costa Brava
Costa Brava no sé qué de la Costa Brava
you know and I didn't know why the [ __ ] she
sabes y yo no sabía por qué [__] me
was telling me This was like what happened with
estaba diciendo Esto fue como lo de
Talavera they also released a clip of mine
talavera que también sacaron un clip mío
where I asked I don't remember
donde yo le preguntaba a no me acuerdo
who she was with and live I said
con quién estaba y en directo que dije
Hey but Talavera What is it you know but
Oye pero Talavera Qué es sabes pero
why the unep There was an unep that a
porque la unep Había una unep que una
girl said she had been to the unep
chica decía que había estado en la unep
Talavera of course when I ask This
talavera claro yo cuando pregunto Esto
is not that I don't know that I don't have to
no es que no sepa que tampoco tengo por
know either I mean I'm sure
qué saberlo O sea que yo estoy seguro
that the loser Wilson the stalker not
que al pringao al Wilson al acosador no
Wilson you ask Tania
al Wilson a la Tania le preguntas a lo
maybe about a town in Seville boyuyos and he does
mejor por un pueblo de Sevilla boyuyos y
n't know where it is either And you probably
no sabe tampoco Dónde está Y seguramente
ask him about various coasts of
le preguntas por varias costas de
Portugal and he doesn't know either  where is it I don't have to
Portugal y tampoco sepa dónde está yo no
know where all
tengo por qué saber dónde están todas
the coasts of Spain are nor do I have to
las costas de España ni tengo por qué
know where all the
saber dónde están todos los pueblos
towns are Talavera sounds like me and s a little more because it is more famous but when I ask him about the unep talavera a kiss Magui Thank you very much sweetheart it's not because I don't know what town it is but it's because I don't know if maybe in Catalonia there
porque no sé si a lo mejor en Cataluña
could be a unep called
puede haber una unep que se llame
Talavera or another town called
Talavera o otro pueblo que se llame
Talavera also that could also happen
Talavera también que también puede pasar
or a neighborhood you know and that's why it's still
o un barrio me entiend y por eso a un es
a Talavera you know and chis still
un Talavera me entiendes y chis sigue
without a member Cris you're going to have to
sin miembro Cris te vas a tener que
become a member okay And then here and
hacer miembro tú vale Y luego aquí y
then Here the thing about the Costa Brava turns out to
luego Aquí lo de la Costa Brava resulta
be that the account that I this is a
ser que la cuenta que yo esto es un
sick person but I mean I understand
enfermo pero o sea entiendo
perfectly that these people don't show their
perfectamente que esta gente no enseña
faces and they are stalkers who create
la cara y son acosadores que se crean
email they create accounts to become
email se crean cuentas para hacerse
multi-accounts and they don't do it from their own
multicuenta y no lo hacen desde la suya
because they are not giving their opinion on gossip my
porque no están opinando de salseo yo mi
account is about gossip my account Javi
cuenta es de salseo mi cuenta Javi
oliveira from Twitter which is the most
oliveira de Twitter que es la cuenta más
viral account for gossip Okay my account  I
viral de salseo Vale mi cuenta yo lo
do it with my face and I have my gossip channel
hago con mi cara y yo mi canal de salseo
Why Because I'm giving my opinion and I'm
Por qué Porque yo estoy opinando y yo s
doing gossip but if I did
estoy haciendo salseo pero si yo hiciera
what these people do I would understand if they
lo que hacen esta gente entendería que
did it hidden behind a pseudonym
lo hicieran escondidos en un pseudónimo
because they are
porque son
stalkers it's assumed that you hate me a lot
acosadores se supone que me odias mucho
but you watch absolutely every
pero ves absolutamente cada directo
single live man a live from Dana a
entero tío un directo de la Dana un
live from Dana to release a clip
directo de la Dana para sacar un clip
where I'm talking to a person who
donde yo hablando con una persona que
is calling telling their story okay
está llamando contando su relato vale
okay the whole coast not the whole Costa
vale está toda la costa no toda la Costa
Brava is red no
Brava están roja no
eh I'm telling you the whole coast the whole Costa
eh le digo toda la costa toda la Costa
Brava I'm not telling you the whole Costa Brava
Brava no le digo toda la Costa Brava
is red not on red alert no Well
están roja no en alerta roja no Bueno
this means that I don't know where
pues esto significa que yo no sé dónde
the Costa Brava is because I'm a hick
está la Costa Brava porque soy un paleto
which I don't have to be eh I
que tampoco tendría por qué serlo eh o
mean I don't have to
sea que tampoco tendría por qué
know it either I mean I have the
conocerlo o sea yo yo tengo los estudios
basic studies and what I do is
básicos y yo a lo que me dedico es al
gossip on YouTube and I inform myself a lot and I
salseo de YouTube y Me informo mucho y
really like to find out things when I'm
me gusta mucho enterarme de cosas cuando
going to talk about it okay but the thing is
voy a hablar de ella vale pero es que
this this live is from November 3rd
este este directo es del 3 de noviembre
and what I'm telling you is true
y lo que le estoy diciendo es verdad el
November 3rd because it had come out
3 de noviembre porque me me había salido
on Twitter in the tweets I was seeing
en Twitter en los twit que estaba viendo
the Costa Brava was on red alert
la Costa Brava estaba en alerta roja
Okay, so she takes it as if to say Okay and
Vale pues lo coge como diciendo Vale y
so my poor thing who also
la tan la pobrecita mía que también le
pays attention to all the harassment accounts of
da bola a todas las cuentas de acoso por
course some are their moderators
supuesto algunos son sus moderadores
okay of course the harassment accounts
vale por supuesto las cuentas de acoso
okay implying that that
vale dando a entender que eso
meant that I that I had said
significaba que yo que yo había dicho
that the Costa Brava was in Valencia I'm telling you that I
que la Costa Brava estaba en Valencia te
'm telling her the
estoy diciendo que le estoy diciendo la
so-called the Costa Brava is on
llamada la Costa Brava está en alera
red alert no yes yes it was
roja no sí sí lo estaba
okay this other one from the creators of
vale esto otro de los creadores de
learn geography with javil veira now
aprende geografía con javil veira ahora
comes learn spelling and they take a clip
llega aprende ortografía y cogen un clip
in which I am playing yesterday with the
en el que yo estoy jugando ayer con las
kids from the kids' club
con los chavales de la chavalería
joking with them as if I was getting
bromeando con ellos como que me estaba
angry that they were all
enfadando que lo estaban todos
understanding it perfectly eh W no
entendiendo perfectamente eh W no hay
problem as long as they don't say something that is
problema mientras no digan algo que es
extremely strange there is no there it says
extremadamente raro no hay ahí dice
perfectly that you can call
perfectamente que se le puede llamar a
the
la
vb you want to suck my ass those of you who
vb me queréis chupar el nepe los que me
are telling me in the chat that they are
estáis diciendo en el chat que están
correctly eliminated but if you
correctamente eliminados pero si lo
are listening to it I'm going to slap you
estáis escuchando Te voy a pegar un
that I'm going to take you away  the little series
bofetón que te voy a quitar la serilla
Okay, I'm here joking around with the
Bueno estoy aquí de broma con los
kids getting angry yelling at me doing
chavales enfadando gritándome haciendo
silly things and they take it as something real well
tontería y lo toman como algo real bueno
the stalker knows very well just like he
el acosador sabe de sobra al igual que
knew about the Costa Brava the stalker
sabía lo de la Costa Brava el acosador
knows very well that I'm because he
sabe de sobra que estoy de porque se
swallows all the live streams they swallow all the
traga todos los directos se tragan todos
live streams every day to see what
los directo todos los días para ver qué
click I give it another meaning okay This is
click le doy otro sentido vale Esto es
a test of the squid game in
una prueba del juego del calamar en el
which they disqualified a kid because he
que descalificaron un chaval porque
called the v a kid from Argentina
llamó a la v un chaval de Argentina
called B the v okay it's possible it was
llamó B a la v vale que se puede que era
valid in the test because they were
válido en la prueba porque estaba
allowed to call the letters as they
permitido que llamasen a las letras como
call them in their country in their region okay
las llaman en su país en su región vale
the age Javi No no no the age For
la edad Javi No no no la edad Por
example I can I can think that for
ejemplo yo puedo yo puedo pensar que por
example this lady if it's because of age
ejemplo esta señora si es por la edad
this lady is the same as the one on the account
esta señora es igual que el de la cuenta
okay And and all those who are following
vale Y y todos los que están siguiendo
here look at this lady Look at
aquí mira la señora esta Mira la señora
this lady Pilar Vera Comment on Wilson when
esta Pilar Vera Comenta en Wilson cuando
he comments when he shares it you see that he
lo comenta cuando lo comparte lo ves que
is quoting Javier canino and he comments
está citando a Javier canino y comenta
on Javier canino's tweet okay look
en el twit de Javier canino vale mira
why this lady is sharing
porque esta señora va compartiendo en su
each tweet on her Twitter  I mean, they are terrible, they are
Twitter cada tweet o sea están fatal
terrible,
están fatal
look They are
mira Son
stalkers, don't you understand, B is B, he doesn't see
acosadores no se entera la B es B no ve
long, he only sees B, the v is v, v or
larga solo ve solo B la v es v v o b
short b, lady, I am amazed, you are another
corta señora estoy asombrada eres otra
stalker, what the [ __ ] are you talking about if you don't
acosadora qué [__] estás hablando si no
know what click is about, we say
sabes de lo que va el click decimos las
both ways, short B or b but it was
dos formas B corta o b pero que era
valid, damn, where is it? I just put it?
válido [__] Dónde está lo acabo de poner
Ah, I closed it. Put the ra, it is valid, it
Ah lo he cerrado lo Pon la ra es válido
was valid, they
era válido
also disqualified the kid when,
también descalificaron al chaval cuando
The kid had done it right. Because
El chaval lo había hecho bien Porque
look, here it says, in Argentina it is also
mira aquí lo pone en Argentina también
called B. I understand if you are spelling
se le llama B entiend si tú estás
quickly, then you call him B, he does
deletreando rápidamente pues le llamas B
n't see girl, he doesn't see little or anything, he
no ve chica ni ve chiquita ni nada lo
said it fluently, okay. And all the
dijo de corrido vale Y todos los
stalkers are applauding a click in
acosadores aplaudiendo un click en el
which I am supposed to be making a
que se supone que yo me estoy
mistake, but everything like that, eh. Of course,
equivocando pero así todo eh Pues claro
eh, head on your knees, if you put yourself Good
eh cabeza rodilla si te pones Buenas
night, if you put your head on your knees, to
noches si te pones cabeza rodilla a
pay attention to what they happen to you. Those
echarle cuenta a lo que te pasan Esas
accounts, well, now you look ridiculous, you just ended up
cuentas pues ahora quedas en rid
like how you just ended up now, you just
acabas de cómo acabas de quedar ahora
ended up, you just ended up making a fool of yourself like
acabas acabas de quedar en ridículo como
all of you who put those kinds of accounts,
todos los que ponéis ese tipo de cuentas
yeah  you follow stalkers and you rely on
si tú sigues a acosadores y te basas en
stalkers and you applaud stalkers you are a
acosadores y aplaudes acosadores eres un
stalker and you just ate and you just made a
acosador y te acabas de comer y acabas
fool of yourself for an edited cli
de quedar en ridículo por un cli editado
It's that this cli Cristiano Ronaldo
Es que este cli Cristiano Ronaldo no
is not there shirtless I'm going to give you a
está ahí sin camiseta te lo voy
preview
adelantando
for not being healthy Ronaldo is not there
por no lo sano ronal no está ahí sin
shirtless eh I'm going to give you a
camiseta eh Ya te lo ya te lo voy
preview in case you I mean he
adelantando por si te I claro él se ha
ate the clip like they're laughing
comido el clip como que se están riendo
at me the one from Troy still here still
de mí al de Troya todavía aquí todavía
here with Michelin star with his nipples
aquí con Michelin sillo con las tetillas
like that and everything last year still here there's
así y todo el año pasado todavía aquí ya
no comparison with you my life This
no hay comparación contigo mi vida Esto
is a normal body I was going to
es un cuerpo normal y corriente iba a
compare and I'm taking pictures for
comparar y me estoy haciendo fotos para
the nutritionist It's that I would put this I
la nutricionista Es que esto lo pondría
imagine that these photos were
yo me imagino que estas fotos las han
taken from the video of the physical change okay
sacado del vídeo del cambio físico vale
that video is already deleted because
que ese vídeo ya lo tengo borrado porque
that was a collaboration with that
eso fue una colaboración con esa
nutritionist okay
nutricionista vale
and now I'm doing something else Now
y ahora estoy haciendo otra cosa Ahora
I'm on a long road of training
estoy en un largo camino de entrenar
hard every day and following a
duro todos los días y siguiendo una
diet every day that is not
dieta todos los días que no están
strict it's a long road okay But
estricta es un camino de fondo vale Pero
this is that  I was just taking pictures
esto es que me iba haciendo fotos sin
okay But this is a normal body I
más vale Pero esto es un cuerpo normal o
mean it's not a laughing body they're
sea no es un cuerpo de risa se están
laughing at something else here and you ate
riendo aquí de otra cosa y te has comido
the bite you ate an edited cli dude
el bite te has comido un cli editado tío
that's what it's
eso es lo que
worth And on top of that taking B the mother that me Of
vale Y encima sacando B la madre que me
course because they are photos for that of Troy I
Claro porque son fotos para eso de Troya
hadn't seen that Oh I hadn't
eso no lo había visto Ay que no lo había
seen it Oh let's see already being good And since it
visto Ay a ver ya ya siendo bueno Y como
's me it seems very good to me that I
soy yo est me parece muy bien que te
take a picture of the Before and after
haga una foto del Antes y del después
but that's fine when The
pero eso está bien cuando Ya termina la
operation is over hottie copying that one of
operación buenorro copiando aquella de
Marta r operation hottie already when
Marta r operación buenorro ya cuando
all that is over take out The before and
acabe de todo eso saca El antes y el
after I have still seen and Kari without a
después todavía he visto y Kari sin
shirt neither the before nor after
camiseta ni el antes ni el después
doing the same operation But he has
haciendo la misma operación Pero él ha
been constant Because when you
sido constante Porque tú cuando
started this you abandoned it
empezaste esto lo dejaste abandonado
but eh karism if he has taken pictures in a t-
pero eh karism si ha sacado fotos en
shirt he has a video uploaded that
camiseta tiene un vídeo subido que lo
IB commented on Hey look I don't know why you laughed at
comentó IB Oye mira no sé por qué os reí
the content I am making the content
el contenido estoy agando el contenido
no dude don't think I'm posting that
no tío no se cree que estoy poniendo esa
photo bragging without comments
foto presumiendo sin comentarios
no well these are already dead bodies
no bueno estos ya son cuerpos muertos
these are already dead bodies  Javier
estos ya son cuerpos muertos Javier
oliveira I haven't produced this yet
oliveira esto yo todavía no lo he
eh first because no cosag
producido eh primero porque no cosag
poce eh this Hello the free city no How
poce eh esto Hola la ciudad libre no Qué
horrible not everyone doesn't have a
horror no todo el mundo no tiene cuerpo
gym body or a tablet or anything like that
de gimnasio ni tableti ni nada de eso
Amazon let's be honest it's not
Amazona vamos a ser sincero tampoco es
that I'm overweight or that I have
que esté desfasado de gordo ni que tenga
a good body rubble almost what is
un bueno cuerpo escombro casi lo que se
called a bought body wants to go of a
llama cuerpo compro quiere ir de de
muscular guy from the gym and he doesn't have
Chico musculado de gimnasio y no tiene
the body dude it's going to be that no maybe
el cuerpo tío va a ser que no a lo mejor
now maybe now that you cover up
ahora a lo mejor ahora que te tapas
so much that you're covering up so much beauty
tanto que estás cubriendo tanta belleza
but when you made that video noo No yes
pero cuando hiciste ese vídeo noo No sí
the old hen of good broth That
la gallina vieja de buen caldo Ya esa
photo original version was already
foto versión original ya era suficiente
ridiculous enough there was no need to edit it
ridícula no hacía falta editarla
completely but it has been so
totalmente pero se ha quedado tan a
comfortable eh I mean it has eaten an edit from
gusto eh o sea se ha comido un edit de
any stalker account of this
cualquier cuenta de acosadores de esto
that manipulate the cli every day it
que manipulan los cli todos los días lo
has reacted like a cli eh that was like that and it has
ha reaccionado como un cli eh que era
been so Pancho and it has
así y ha quedado tan Pancho y se ha
been so Pancho it is already to take for
quedado tan Pancho ya está a tomar por
ass okay
culo vale